http://accutherm.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyYou are here: Home / Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
AccuTherm respects your privacy and the limited purpose for which our site visitors provide us their personal information.  By using this site, you consent to AccuTherm’s privacy policy, detailed below.
Information Collected
Generally, AccuTherm does not collect personal information through the use of its website, except such personal information as you provide by sending an e-mail via the “mail to:” function or filling out a “Contact Form” to request a quote or product information. AccuTherm may save the contact information you provide.  AccuTherm will not share, sell or rent any of the information collected through its website to any unauthorized third parties, and does not intend to do so in the future.  AccuTherm, or one of its trusted third-party sales representatives, may use the information provided to AccuTherm to contact you in the future by postal service, e-mail or telephone to convey information about our products, solutions or services that we feel may benefit you.  Such authorized third parties will keep any personal information provided to them by AccuTherm for the purpose of contacting you to discuss products, solutions or services in the strictest confidence.  Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this policy, AccuTherm may release personal information when it believes that the release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce its site policies or to protect its rights or the rights, property or safety of others.
Information Collected by Others
This notice addresses AccuTherm’s privacy policy only, and does not address the privacy policies of any other websites that users may access via links from our site.  AccuTherm is not responsible for the information collection policies of other websites, for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our website, nor for the information or content contained therein.   Often, links to other websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to our visitors.  Users are advised to review the privacy policies of other websites carefully with respect to the collection and use of private information.
Cookies
Cookies are small text files collected by websites from a user’s browser, which may include an anonymous unique identifier.  Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your computer’s hard drive.  AccuTherm’s website uses Cookies for the sole purpose of third party traffic analytics, such as Google Analytics and Hubspot.  These cookies collect information anonymously, such as the time that you visited the AccuTherm website, whether you have been to the AccuTherm website before, and what site referred you to our website, then reports website trends without identifying individual users.  We use that information to generate reports and help us improve our website.  You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent without affecting the usability of the AccuTherm website.
Updating, Correcting, and Deleting Personal Information
Contact information provided to us through the “mail to” or “Contact Us” form on the AccuTherm Website is stored perpetually.  You may update or correct your personal information provided to AccuTherm through our website at any time.   To do so, please send an e-mail to sales@accutherm.com with the subject line “Update Personal Information.”  If you would like to have your personal information removed from our records, please send an e-mail to sales@accutherm with the subject line “Remove Personal Information.”
Periodic Policy Changes
AccuTherm reserves the right to review and change this privacy policy at any time.  To ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our privacy policy, please bookmark and periodically review this page.  This policy was last updated on September 24, 2018.
Contact Information
AccuTherm
425 Hanley Industrial Ct.
St. Louis, MO 63144
Toll Free: (800) 243-8162
Phone: (314) 644-4300
Fax: (314) 644-5332
Website: www.accutherm.com
E-mail: sales@accutherm.com
CERTIFICATIONS Our heaters are currently UL recognized, CSA compliant and CE approved. We are ASME and National Board certified for Section VIII Div 1 Pressure Vessel Welding.
Additionally, we have built heaters to Military standards for the Army, Navy, Coast Guard and DCSC. We have designed and built systems to Canadian pressure vessel codes CRN, ABSA & TSSA. We also meet certain NSF, NACE and API standards.
PopularHow to Calculate KW Requirements for Typical Heater App...November 30, 2015 - 4:40 pmBenefits of Using Custom Heaters vs StandardDecember 19, 2014 - 7:04 am873 Series Quick Ship Contactor Control PanelFebruary 19, 2016 - 2:52 pmInfrared Heating: Much More than TemperatureDecember 3, 2014 - 11:17 pmRecent870 Series SCR Control PanelMarch 3, 2016 - 11:04 am873 Series Quick Ship SCR Control PanelMarch 1, 2016 - 9:53 amHeater Applications: Power GenerationFebruary 26, 2016 - 11:59 amRadiant HeatersFebruary 25, 2016 - 9:58 amCommentsHow to calculate the total kwh energy
to heat up &...November 4, 2020 - 10:36 pm by Yogeshwar RaikohadAmazing tips for electric heater elements. I will consider...October 30, 2020 - 5:20 am by Shiva HeatersWe want to use carbon fiber infrared heater 2000 KW x 22...July 27, 2020 - 6:49 am by Hashim A. HussainGood evening, I was just visiting your site and filled out...June 29, 2020 - 3:45 am by Hildred LeTags
Scroll to top
